[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
PREVIOUSLY
[distorted voice] Detective Jin,
did you think the game was over?
Round 2.
[glass shattering]
Detective Jin, you got lucky.
For now, I think we should move
Detective Jin to a safe house.
[Changun] Put Team 1 with him.
You can trust them.
[scoffs]
[Isoo] It's a box I've never seen before.
[timer beeping]
-What?
-It's a bomb!
[tires screeching]
What's going on?
There's a bomb in the car.
Blast radius is 50... No, 100 meters.
Take the wheel.
[tires screeching]
[Hyera] Four minutes left.
[Isoo] I know a place.
[siren blaring]
[grunts]
[Hyera] There are people here. Be careful.
[car horn honking]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
-Detective Park, stop!
-[tires screech]
[siren blaring]
[tires screech]
-Nine seconds.
-Open the door.
-What?
-Open the door!
[timer continues beeping]
Three, two, one!
[grunts]
[heavy thud]
[groans]
[muffled explosion]
STYLE
::cue()
[both panting]
[Hyera grunts softly]
[Isoo grunts]
[Hyera grunts]
[exhales sharply]
[both continue panting]
[car approaching]
-[tires screech]
-[car door opens]
[Kyungjin] Bro!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
That was way too close.
Are you all right?
Yes.
We need a different location.
I don't know how far ahead they planned.
[vehicles approaching]
[siren blaring]
Get Detective Jin out of here
before backup arrives.
Understood.
You're okay, right?
Yes.
[Junyoung exhales sharply]
Violent Crimes' car exploded?
-Yes, sir.
-[gasps]
You mean, the bomber came
to the police station
and planted a bomb in our car?
-[sighs softly]
-This is a nightmare.
What are we going to do?
The press is waiting.
So what?
-You handle it.
-Sir.
Don't look at me.
Go out there and deal with it!
[scoffs] I can't believe this.
[breathing heavily]
[♪ tense music playing]
[reporters chattering]
[reporter 1] Can you tell us
what happened?
We heard a police vehicle had exploded.
[reporter 2] Was
Detective Jin Isoo inside?
[reporter 3] Any casualties?
-[reporter 4] Did you catch them?
-Who's behind this?
[reporters clamoring]
[clamor subsides]
There are no casualties.
We'll place this case under embargo
until the investigation is complete.
[reporter 5] Embargo?
We've already had
two large-scale explosions.
We don't know what the culprit is after.
We can't risk provoking them.
Please cooperate.
[clamor resumes]
[Isoo sighs]
Where are we?
The safest place we have right now.
Let's go inside.
[Isoo sighs]
ECSTASY
A BREATHLESS FALL
CLIMAX
LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What's with the decor here? Huh?
STYLE
::cue()
MS. JOO HYERA
-Is this Joo Hyera's place?
-Yeah.
The bomber would never expect it.
[Isoo] Yeah.
I didn't expect it either.
I'm going to a hotel.
Hey, come on. Why?
Because she embarrassed me on national TV,
and she keeps bossing me around
like she's our team leader.
Hey, Jin Isoo.
She offered up her home to keep you safe.
Stop being so petty.
[Kyungjin] He's right. You should rest.
You've had a really stressful day.
Where's the bedroom?
It's this way. Come on, bro.
[Isoo sighs in exasperation]
[Kyungjin] God, we need a team leader.
This way, bro.
[Isoo sighs]
[scoffs]
That evil woman
likes cute things like this?
[grunting]
Why're you lying on the floor?
I don't sleep in other people's beds.
Go. I'm going to sleep.
Night, bro.
[door closes]
What about Isoo?
He went to sleep.
Okay. Good job today.
You go back to the station.
I'll stay here.
Got it.
[sighs]
MISSED CALL
JIWON
[sighs]
INCOMING CALL
JIWON
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello? Jiwon, sorry--
[Dr. Yoon] What happened?
Are you okay? Where are you?
Uh, Jiwon.
Calm down. One question at a time.
How can I be calm?
A car exploded at the Hangang River.
Isoo's unharmed.
-We're now at a safe house, so--
-And you?
What?
Are you okay?
I was really worried.
Yes, I'm completely fine.
[sighs in relief]
Do you know how scared I was?
Who on earth would do something like this?
Exactly.
This is the third incident now.
I'm sure we'll find some evidence.
I need Team 2 to go over the footage
from the launch event again.
Let me know if you see
any suspicious movements.
[in English] Okay. [in Korean] Come on.
-[detective 1] Okay.
-[detective 2] Okay.
Let's check
the parking lot security footage.
Got it.
[sighs softly]
[mouse clicks]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[music fades]
[groans softly]
[cell phone vibrates]
[distorted voice, in English] Final Round.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[in Korean] Come alone.
He'll blow up if I see anyone else.
You know where this is.
MR. CHOI
[line ringing]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed...
[music swells, fades]
[keyboard clacks]
[sighs heavily] Did you find anything?
No.
No one approached the vehicle.
Then how did they put the bomb in there?
When was the vehicle last used?
Three days ago.
Let's check the nearby dashcams
in the morning.
Okay.
By the way,
what about Park Gyeongtae?
[♪ ominous music plays]
We've been watching him,
but he never left his house.
[sighs]
My team will retrieve
the vehicle tomorrow.
-Go get some shut-eye.
-Okay.
[sighs softly]
[sighs heavily]
[cell phone snaps shut]
[♪ gripping music playing]
[shower running]
NEARBY PARKED VEHICLE RECORDS
[music fades]
[line connects, ringing]
Yes, sir.
Sorry for disturbing you so early.
I couldn't reach you yesterday.
You parked in front
of a Violent Crimes vehicle.
I need to check your dashcam footage.
Yes, please call me when you arrive.
I'll come up to get it.
[line disconnects]
-I'll contact the rest of the list.
-Okay.
Sorry, I left on my own.
Even if I end up dead,
you guys are not at fault.
Park Junyoung, Choi Kyungjin...
Thanks for everything.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Good luck.
-Thanks.
Hey, here you go.
-Thank you.
-Take care.
Yes, sir.
STYLE
::cue()
THIRD INCIDENT
POLICE VEHICLE BOMB ATTACK
HIGH-YIELD AMMONIUM NITRATE IED
100-METER BLAST RADIUS
[music intensifies]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense music playing]
[sighs in exasperation]
[line connects, ringing]
[cell phone vibrating]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed...
[sighs wearily] Isoo.
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
What?
Understood.
-What's wrong?
-Isoo disappeared.
-Did he take Detective Park's car?
-I think so.
-I'll head out now. You track him down.
-Got it.
[engine revving]
There he is.
Please track license plate 9832.
[officer] Got it.
[cell phone ringing]
-[Kyungjin] Ma'am.
-Yes, where's Detective Jin?
Near his family estate.
The address is 251 Pyeongjin-dong.
I'll head over there, so keep me updated.
-And let Detective Park know, too.
-Yes, ma'am.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[panting]
What are you doing here?
I got a DM.
I was told to come here and film you die.
GO FILM HIM DIE
BE THERE, OR ELSE
It's my mom.
[cell phone vibrates]
[distorted voice] Head inside together.
We're being watched.
Let's go inside.
Mr. Choi!
[cell phone vibrates]
[distorted voice] Turn on the camera.
Unless you want to see your mom die.
[♪ enthralling music playing]
[cell phone vibrates]
[music fades]
Turn around.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[gasps in fear] Detective! Detective Jin!
Over here.
There's a bomb in the car.
Blast radius is 50... No, 100 meters.
[Isoo] Follow me.
[grunts] There's a bunker here.
[gasps in disbelief]
[timer beeping]
[clangs]
[metallic creak]
-[cell phone vibrates]
-Hello?
He's at Jin Myeongchul's house.
I think Jin Isoo has been set up.
[sighs]
Please alert local police
and emergency services.
I will.
-Be careful.
-Yes, sir.
[Hyeonwoo panting frantically]
[timer continues beeping]
[continues panting]
It should've gone off by now.
[mouse clicking]
[camera chimes]
[Hyeonwoo breathing heavily]
[keyboard clacking]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
That bastard was bluffing.
[scoffs]
[gasps in horror]
Detective!
[panting frantically]
[timer beeping]
[music intensifies, fades]
[tires screech]
[engine shuts off]
[explosion]
[♪ tense music playing]
Detective Jin!
Jin Isoo, where are you?
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Isoo sighs in relief]
[coughs] Over here.
Are you okay? What happened?
[panting]
Why is the Assistant Director here?
It's a long story.
Let's get out of here first.
[hurried footsteps approaching]
Hey.
You okay?
[sighs wearily]
You asshole!
You...
If something had happened to you...
I didn't have a choice.
Let's get out of here first.
[grunts in frustration]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[sirens blaring]
[brakes squeal]
[Isoo] It was because of this.
But he wasn't here?
No.
[sighs] Then what could've happened?
[Hyera] Was he taken somewhere else?
Maybe the photo was just a bait.
The photo was definitely taken here.
[Kyungjin] Chairman Choi is here.
-[Isoo] Mr. Choi.
-Yes.
Are you all right?
Did you get hurt?
What about you?
Where were you?
I was traveling by helicopter.
Then how did you know to come here?
You didn't answer when I called you back,
so I contacted Detective Choi.
[sighs softly]
You should call your mother.
[line connects, ringing]
Hello? Mom, where are you?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
At the sauna?
God, Mom! I really can't with you.
-I'm hanging up.
-[line disconnects]
So this was just a deepfake.
Then why bomb this place?
Using a fake photo, no less.
To kill me.
We should go. It's too dangerous.
[Hyera] Wait.
You said the bomber's watching.
[ticking]
[♪ tense music playing]
[onlookers murmuring]
[♪ ominous music plays]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
The unexploded bomb was defused on site,
and it's currently being analyzed.
FORENSICS
[♪ soft suspenseful music playing]
[Hyera] Jang Hyeonwoo is hiding out
at a nearby motel.
[coughing]
And I've relocated Detective Jin.
Where?
[birds chirping]
[♪ serene music playing]
[Isoo exclaims in satisfaction]
I haven't been over in so long.
[grunts]
[Mr. Choi] Go wash up.
I'll make you something to eat.
In a minute.
[chuckles] Quickly, come on.
There you go. [grunts]
[exhales deeply]
[chuckles softly]
[Isoo exclaims in satisfaction]
This house seems too small
for the chairman of the Hansu Group.
Do you want a bigger place?
I like it here.
And I like you, Mr. Choi.
[chuckles]
Have a seat.
[sighs contentedly]
CHOI JEONGHUN
Are you unwell?
No, it's just a little indigestion.
Did you get it checked out?
I will.
Go on.
[chair clatters]
[breathes deeply]
I haven't had porridge in a while.
Mmm.
-[Mr. Choi] How is it?
-It's seasoned perfectly.
STYLE
::cue()
-Just as I expected.
-[chuckles]
Mmm. Mmm.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
We got a partial print.
Submit it for expedited analysis.
It's really urgent.
-Did they find something?
-[Hyera] Yes.
A partial print. It'll take a while.
FOURTH INCIDENT
Four bomb attacks,
but only one partial fingerprint.
We should've found something
at the event site or the parking lot.
Anything on the security footage?
We checked all the parking lot cameras
and dashcams.
Everything up to two days
before the incident.
[exhales heavily]
It wasn't here.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
No one's bold enough
to plant a bomb at a police station.
-You went to the first site in that car?
-Yes.
They lured you there to plant the bomb.
I'll get their security footage.
ANONYMOUS TIPSTER
[Isoo sighs]
Who could be behind all this?
[sighs deeply]
Yeah, who could it be?
Who would want me...
[high-pitched ringing]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[Junyoung] Don't touch that!
-[exhales, grunts]
-[timer beeping rapidly]
[distorted voice] Come alone.
He'll blow up if I see anyone else.
[groans in pain]
-[muffled bang]
-[high-pitched ringing continues]
-[Mr. Choi] What's wrong?
-Detective!
-[glass shattering]
-[muffled explosion]
[Isoo exhales sharply]
[distant tinkling]
[grunts in pain]
-[music stops]
-Drink this.
[grunts]
[gulps]
[exhales shakily]
Are you all right?
[panting] Yeah.
I just...
couldn't breathe for a second.
[sighs]
You should go to the hospital.
[pants]
If you go first.
[pants] I'm fine.
[exhales deeply]
I really don't know who it could be.
But why make it so complicated?
Planting bombs at four locations
and even using a deepfake?
Why not just plant it at your house?
[Seungju] It probably isn't revenge.
The Isoo I know
would never make someone
want revenge this badly.
It might be
driven by desire.
-[pops]
-[clangs]
-[timer beeps]
-[explosion]
[gasps] Mr. Choi.
You know my dad's house.
Do you remember it had a bunker?
Yes, of course.
The bomb went off in there,
which is how I survived.
But it blew a hole in the floor.
STYLE
::cue()
I got the footage
from Hansu Department Store.
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicking]
[sighs] We won't be able to see anything.
We got a match on the fingerprint.
Jang Hyeonsuk. No criminal record.
He works in R&D at Mirae Electronics.
JANG HYEONSUK
-Should we go bring him in?
-Yes.
-Let's go.
-Right.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
FIRST INCIDENT
HANSU DEPARTMENT STORE
[Hyera] The first bomb
had a simple design.
Its target was Jin Isoo.
SECOND INCIDENT
The second bomb...
[glass shattering]
It was used to prove they meant business.
THIRD INCIDENT
POLICE VEHICLE
The third bomb...
[muffled explosion]
We need a different location.
I don't know how far ahead they planned.
It sent Jin Isoo to a safe house
and isolated him.
FOURTH INCIDENT
The fourth bomb...
It finally tried to kill Jin Isoo,
but failed because there was a bunker
in the house?
[inhales deeply]
No, that's not it.
There were three explosions.
How could there be no casualties?
[music intensifies, fades]
The bomber wasn't trying to kill Jin Isoo.
[door slides open]
[Mr. Choi exhales deeply]
[sharp gasp]
Do you seriously only own suits?
I even go hiking in a suit.
God, you're so buttoned-up.
It's my fashion philosophy.
By the way, where are you going?
[inhales] I think
I know what the bombers are after.
It could be dangerous.
That looks even more dangerous.
This is great!
It's unique.
STYLE
::cue()
They weren't trying to kill me.
It was all a ruse.
I'll go catch them.
[sighs]
-[cell phone vibrates]
-Hello?
Yes, Director. This is Joo Hyera.
Whose idea was it to do a feature
on Detective Jin Isoo?
It was Assistant Director Jang Hyeonwoo.
He said he's a fan of Detective Jin.
Right. Okay.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[cell phone snaps shut]
-That was random.
[line connects, ringing]
Hello, this is Joo Hyera.
Could you check
if Jang Hyeonwoo is inside his room?
Yes, right away.
[line disconnects]
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicks]
[♪ tense music playing]
[keyboard key clacks]
JANG HYEONSUK
SIBLING JANG HYEONWOO
[digital beeping]
He used the van to block him from view.
Jang Hyeonwoo.
Jang Hyeonsuk.
PYEONGJIN-DONG ESTATE BOMB ATTACK
251 PYEONGJIN-DONG, SEONGBUK-GU
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Jang Hyeonwoo's not here.
[cell phone vibrating]
Detective Park.
[Junyoung clicks tongue]
We can't locate Jang Hyeonsuk.
He hasn't shown up for work either.
-Meet me at Jin Myeongchul's house.
-[Junyoung] Got it.
Let's go.
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[tires screech]
Joo Hyera?
What's with the badass look?
It's for mobility.
And you? Are you Indiana Jones?
[sighs sarcastically]
Too bad I don't have a whip.
-What made you come here?
-[inhales deeply]
I just couldn't figure out how
they planted the bomb inside the house.
Unless the Assistant Director
brought it in.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[panting frantically]
I can do this.
I can do it.
Detective! Detective Jin!
[digital beeping]
[timer beeping]
What about you? How did you know?
We got a fingerprint off the bomb
by the entrance.
It's Jang Hyeonwoo's brother.
They used to live at this address.
And their mother died five years ago.
Oh...
-You're actually pretty sharp.
-[scoffs]
Their target was the bunker, right?
Yes.
The whole thing was a setup
to blow up that place.
Because I'm the only one who can open it.
-[grunts] There's a bunker here.
-[clangs]
[metallic creak]
-[gasps in disbelief]
-Mr. Choi told me
that an extremely
wealthy family used to live here.
When their business went under, they sold
the house to my dad 30 years ago,
but for the last two years or so,
that family kept trying
to buy the house back.
What's in this house?
Good question. Shall we go find out?
[muffled voices]
[thudding footsteps]
[Hyeonsuk] Hey, I'll grab that end. Move.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[whispering] Looks like
they're already here.
-[muffled clattering]
-[muffled chatter continues]
[Hyeonsuk] Okay, lift on three.
[Hyeonwoo and Hyeonsuk grunting]
[Hyeonsuk] Hey, I'll grab that end. Move.
-Lift. One, two, three.
-[both grunting]
-Hyeonsuk!
-Properly.
I told you to bring a dolly.
-Okay, okay.
-It's so heavy.
Think this is gold?
How much would it be worth?
Enough to live our dreams, of course.
STYLE
::cue()
[both chuckle]
[Hyeonsuk] I'm going to throw
my resignation right in my manager's face.
You?
Me? I want fried chicken.
-Just chicken? Not even omakase?
-So tasty.
[both panting]
-Tie it on nice and tight.
-Okay.
I'll go up first and pull it up.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
[grunts]
[panting]
Give me a minute.
[♪ upbeat jazz music playing]
-[gasps]
-[shushes]
[gasps softly]
[gun cocks]
[exhales] The police.
You came to arrest me.
[exclaims]
Hyeonsuk, I got it!
I'll tie it up!
[Isoo scatting]
Be quiet.
[Isoo humming]
[Hyeonwoo] Hyeonsuk, did you open it?
Come out.
[exhales deeply]
Don't even think about running.
Where would you go anyway? Come here.
Good job.
[grunting]
I'm worn out from pulling that up,
so you can cuff yourself.
Thanks.
What could this be?
Put the cuffs on. It's okay.
[latch rattling]
[thuds]
[lid creaks]
[gasps]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What is it? Is it gold?
Or diamonds?
Do you want to know?
I'm not telling you.
[sighs]
[exclaims]
Take them away.
-[scoffs]
-[handcuffs click]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[Hyeonwoo] Our dad died of cancer
two years ago,
and he left one final instruction.
That house... [coughs, wheezes]
You and your brother
must get that house back.
In that place...
rests our family's
most valuable possession.
[whimpers]
Just do as I say.
[exhales sharply]
We didn't believe him.
But our relatives who came to the funeral
said something different.
What happened to the treasure?
Treasure?
Father gave it to Hyeonwoo's grandfather,
didn't he?
[elderly woman] Yes.
That house.
Father gave it to him.
The house? The house I was born in?
[sighs] We sold that house years ago.
That house has been sold.
Yes, it's been sold.
When you sold it,
didn't you take out the chest?
What chest?
The treasure chest.
[scoffs] Oh, come on. There's no treasure.
Unless you saw it yourself...
I saw it.
I saw Father bury the chest there.
You saw it too, didn't you?
I did.
In the dead of night,
he secretly buried that chest
by the old well.
It must've been awfully valuable.
He said it should never be lost.
But then a house was built there.
Chairman Jin Myeongchul's house.
What was inside that chest?
Gold.
I told your dad
when I went to visit him in the hospital.
Nonsense.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You two were imagining things.
[softly] Gold.
Even then, I didn't believe it. But...
Buy that house back, no matter the cost.
The chest is still there.
I need to get it
before those brats catch on.
It was mine to begin with.
Jackpot.
[♪ suspenseful music plays]
So, that's why you tried to kill me?
[exclaims] We weren't trying to kill you.
Yeah. We worked so hard
to make sure nobody got hurt.
We set them off when no one was around.
[♪ ominous music plays]
I almost died three times.
-That was all part of--
-[Hyeonwoo] Sorry.
Sorry.
But...
could you just tell us one thing?
What was inside the chest?
We'll serve time, however many years.
So please.
Please tell us just that. Please?
Ah.
Gold.
[gasps]
[breath trembles]
How much was there?
[exhales] Well, at today's gold prices,
around 100 billion won?
[both exclaim excitedly]
[Hyeonwoo] 100 billion won?
[cries joyfully]
-That belongs to us, right?
-Of course, it does.
Of course.
You deserve it
after all you've been through.
STYLE
::cue()
It should be a family heirloom.
Can't you show it to us? Just once?
We risked our lives for this.
Please.
It's ours anyway,
so please let us see it just once.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
Hmm.
[grunts]
You worked hard to find this treasure.
You should at least get to see it.
All right.
[both giggle excitedly]
-Wow.
-We're rich now.
-Wait, what is this?
Wait, hold on.
What?
What the...
[in English] Ready...
Action.
[in Korean] It was a treasure chest that
they orchestrated four bombings to get.
What exactly was inside it?
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[creaking]
The treasure they were
so desperate to find
was none other than...
"JANG DEUKSU"
...a record of collaboration
with Imperial Japan.
The bombers' great-grandfather
was Jang Deuksu.
Also known as "The Master of Torture."
He arrested and tortured
hundreds of independence activists
as a pro-Japanese police officer.
While working as an officer,
Jang Deuksu threatened landowners
into handing over their deeds.
These are those very documents.
Jang Deuksu's sons, Kunkuk and Jongkuk,
sold these lands, amassed a fortune,
and went into postwar reconstruction,
which made them extremely wealthy.
They believed their prosperity
would last forever,
but then a troublemaker was born.
Jang Jongkuk's only son
and the father of the bombers,
Jang Myungjun,
failed at every business he tried.
Perhaps this is what they call
justice prevailing.
JUSTICE WILL PREVAIL
But here's the thing.
Before Jang Myungjun died of cancer,
he told his sons to find the chest
their grandfather had left behind.
The two fools who believed him
orchestrated the bombings
to find this chest.
But what they uncovered...
was evidence
that their family collaborated
with Imperial Japan during the occupation.
It is truly a fitting end
for this collaborationist family.
I suppose another name will be added
to the list of collaborators,
which I plan to publish.
This has been Jin Isoo,
a detective for the people.
[cheering]
That's me. That's me, all right.
A round of applause!
What do you think? Amazing, right?
Yes, amazing.
The comments are blowing up.
"Even busting collaborators,
what can't he do?"
"Just how cool is he?"
Wow, amazing.
My God, just look at this.
-Let's get a beer.
-Yes, sir.
This is insane!
-Look at this.
-Yes, you're amazing.
-Look.
-[Junyoung] Come on. Let's go home.
Where are you going? Come on, admire me.
Bro, you're so cool. The best!
Hey, let's go grab a beer.
Sorry, I have a date.
-Hello? Babe?
-Detective Park.
I have plans, too.
You don't have a girlfriend.
Shut up. See you.
Come on.
[sighs softly]
STYLE
::cue()
Jiwon.
Surprised?
Have you been waiting here for me?
Yes.
Come on, I found this great place to eat.
There's always a long wait.
We should hurry.
[Dr. Yoon chuckles]
-Weren't you cold?
-I'm fine.
Up for a drink again tonight?
-[Junyoung] Sure.
-[Dr. Yoon] Great!
[chuckles]
I knew it.
[sighs] I'm so lonely.
I don't have anyone
to share this afterglow with.
-Getting off work?
-Yes.
Not sure if you saw the show,
but I gave it one heck of an ending.
[♪ quirky music playing]
[Hyera] I didn't see it. I was too busy.
Yes. Of course, you were.
Guess this is goodbye.
Happy?
My face gives me away every time.
Wishing you the best
with the Counterterrorism Team. Good luck.
Right. You stay out of trouble, too.
Take care.
Okay.
[sighs in relief]
[exhales deeply]
[Changun] Joo.
[in English] Would you like
something to drink?
[in Korean] You did a great job.
You too, sir.
Working with you again
felt like old times.
-[chuckles softly]
-I could really count on you.
Me too.
What did you think of Jin Isoo?
[inhales deeply]
He can be a bit odd,
and he's unpredictable,
but he's got good instincts.
And he's quite serious about the job.
Right?
He's actually a decent detective.
Do you have someone lined up
to lead Team 1?
[inhales deeply]
No. [exhales]
No one.
So I was wondering...
[Isoo humming]
Chief! Want to watch the show with me?
I saw it.
Jin Isoo, a detective for the people.
Oh. You're getting a new team leader
on Monday.
-Tell your team not to be late.
-Team leader?
-Who is it?
-Curious?
You bet.
You'll see.
I brought in a solid detective.
We're getting a new team leader?
How very interesting.
[on TV] I suppose another name will be
added to the list of collaborators,
which I plan to publish.
Apply now to receive yours for free.
This has been Jin Isoo,
a detective for the people.
[chuckles softly]
That nutjob.
[♪ upbeat swing jazz music playing]
[Isoo] Put it on.
STYLE
::cue()
You didn't last time.
Your head's on backward. That's it.
Detective Park, wear it.
-[whines]
-Very handsome. Perfect.
Hello!
[crowd cheering]
[Isoo] Hi there! Want a photo?
Okay. One, two, three.
[Junyoung sighs]
He's going overboard again.
[Kyungjin] Come on, it's all good fun.
VIOLENT CRIME TEAM 1
NEW BOSS COMING
Ahh! Post it on social media.
Okay, band.
Let's give it a try.
Just like we practiced. Ready!
[shouts command]
[♪ triumphant brass fanfare playing]
[in English] Stop!
[in Korean] What in the world...
WELCOME, OUR NEW TEAM LEADER
What is all this?
[in Korean] Sir!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Sir.
Come on, clear all this out.
[exclaims scornfully]
-This was...
-Sir!
Jin Isoo's doing.
It's for my new boss. You know the drill.
Oh.
[chuckles]
-Somebody's working hard.
-[Isoo] Of course.
We're getting a new team leader.
Of course.
-Like the flowers?
-Yeah.
-Oh. Incoming!
-Really? My new boss is here?
[whispering] Okay, here we go.
[shouts command]
[♪ triumphant brass fanfare playing]
[engine shuts off]
[music stops]
[♪ dramatic music plays]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
Joo Hyera?
[camera shutters clicking]
-[music fades]
-I didn't expect such a grand welcome.
[chuckles softly]
Detective Jin has been working hard
since morning.
I guess you can be sweet.
This is the new team leader of Violent
Crime Investigation Team 1, Joo Hyera.
She's got years on you boys.
She was on our Violent Crime Team
before moving to Counterterrorism.
[chuckles softly]
Detective Jin,
take good care of your new boss.
Take good care of her.
Detective Jin Isoo,
Detective Park Junyoung,
Detective Choi Kyungjin...
I'm glad to join the team.
STYLE
::cue()
[muttering] This has to be a nightmare.
It's real.
Get used to it.
[microphone feedback]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Looking forward to it, nutjob.
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 2
JIN ISOO AND JOO HYERA MEET AGAIN!
Special Cast.
Kim Uiseong
[Hyera] What's the report about?
[woman] There's a ghost
in the abandoned house.
It's asking us to catch the killer.
Of course I'm not scared.
There's definitely something in there.
[man] You uncovered five bodies?
-I said wait for the warrant.
-I bought the house!
[man] A couple and their son,
a college student, were all murdered.
So the house was abandoned after that,
and then it was used as a burial site.
Police! Please come out, serial killer.
[Hyera] We need to start this case over.
-[muffled] Help me!
-[Isoo] So they're professional killers?
[Hyera] They're methodical and cold.
-There's something here.
-[Isoo] Detective Joo.
Just stay close to me from now on.
The hero never dies that easily.
Meow.
Jin Isoo! Nutjob!
-Yes, ma'am!
-[Hyera] We don't know who attacked us.
-Is there a fire?
-[Isoo] No one's going to die.
Why are you being so dramatic?
There's a fire. The detectives
went inside, but now it's on fire.
How do we get out?
-Hey, Jin Isoo.
-[Isoo] I'm working on it!
Get out of the way.
[♪ pensive music playing]
DISSOLUTION
Translated by Hyesoo Lee